<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docendo Discimus</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Docendo Discimus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>hello-world.Rmd</title>
      <link>/post/hello-world-rmd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hello-world-rmd/</guid>
      <description>Insert Lead paragraph here.
A augue nunc lacus auctor efficitur tempor placerat, dictum volutpat mi vitae viverra porta non sem, himenaeos senectus vivamus potenti cubilia sollicitudin. Curae cursus inceptos tincidunt magna mi nibh ad enim etiam, molestie eu quis primis hendrerit taciti phasellus. Feugiat ultricies dictumst iaculis potenti odio laoreet urna at, ultrices curae leo accumsan proin sem lobortis.
Heading 2 Sollicitudin ornare odio blandit aenean enim lacus accumsan elementum vestibulum porta mauris lorem, ullamcorper class fermentum sem hendrerit ante augue penatibus scelerisque felis leo proin,ad nascetur venenatis sodales dignissim viverra suspendisse turpis convallis condimentum sapien.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DERA</title>
      <link>/portfolio/dera/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/dera/</guid>
      <description>This is a Java reference implementation of dynamic event-driven actors runtime aiming at providing adequate abstraction levels and mechanisms for modelling and developing (distributed) event-based systems. DERA leverages the intrinsic loose coupling of event-driven communication styles to support various kinds of run-time evolution and adaptation (i.e., enabling run-time flexibility) while minimizing the non-deterministic nature of traditional event-based applications (i.e., supporting formal analysis).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hyde-hyde</title>
      <link>/portfolio/hyde-hyde/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/hyde-hyde/</guid>
      <description>Hyde-hyde is a responsive Hugo theme inspired by @spf13&amp;rsquo;s Hyde and its variant Nate Finch&amp;rsquo;s blog. It was heavily restructured with modularised page layouts for easier maintenance and modification. Hyde-hyde offers awesome features such as nice colour tone, code highlighting, Font-Awesome 5&amp;rsquo;s sidebar icons), a cool portfolio page, more choices for commenting (e.g. GraphComment, Disqus).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LaraMod</title>
      <link>/portfolio/laramod/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/laramod/</guid>
      <description>LaraMod is another modularisation effort to systematically organising a Laravel based project. The idea stems from my struggle to structure a Laravel-based project so that I can work effectively on individual modules whilst keeping Laravel codebase intact as much as possible and also keeping the project&amp;rsquo;s codebase separate from Laravel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Hugo</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>